purelyhr.com 2019-03-07

# Privacy Policy | PurelyHR

* * *

## LAST UPDATED: MAY 24, 2018

## 1\. Introduction

This Privacy Policy applies to all the products, services, websites and apps offered by PurelyHR.com, owned and operated by Ironflow Technologies Inc. (collectively “PurelyHR”, “us”, or “we”). We refer to those products, services, websites and apps collectively as the “Services” in this policy. References to "data" in this Privacy Policy will refer to whatever data you use our services to collect, or data inserted on one of our website – either or, it’s all your data. Reference to personal information or just information, means information about you personally that we collect or for which we act as protector. If you want to identify your data controller please see the "Who is my data controller" section below.

## 2\. Information We Collect

### 2.1 Who are “you”?

We refer to “you” a lot in this Privacy Policy. To better understand what information is most relevant to you, see the following useful definitions.

#### Visitors

You are just visiting our website because you are curious, or might be interested in our services.

#### Creators

You created and hold a PurelyHR account, and are using our services to manage your company’s human resources. Creators are data controllers.

#### Users

Your employer (“Creator”) created and hold a PurelyHR account, and you as an employee, have a login to use our services for various reasons, such as submitting time-off requests, viewing your vacation history, filling out timesheets or timecards, or simply review and sign an e-document.

IF YOU ARE AN EMPLOYEE OF A CUSTOMER THAT USES THE PURELYHR SERVICES, PLEASE ALSO REFER TO YOUR EMPLOYER’S PRIVACY POLICY, WHICH APPLIES TO THE COLLECTION, USE, PROCESSING AND RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. EMPLOYEES OF OUR CUSTOMERS WHO SEEK ACCESS TO THEIR DATA, OR WHO SEEK TO UPDATE OR DELETE INACCURATE DATA SHOULD DIRECT THEIR REQUESTS TO THEIR EMPLOYERS WHO ARE PURELYHR’S CUSTOMERS. PURELYHR CUSTOMERS ARE ABLE TO DELETE AND UPDATE PERSONAL INFORMATION AND DATA WITHOUT PURELYHR’S INVOLVEMENT.

### 2.2 Information we collect about you

  * **Contact Information**

You might provide us with your contact information, whether through use of our services, a form on our website, an interaction with our sales or customer support team.

  * **Usage Information**

We collect usage information about you whenever you interact with our websites and services. This includes which web pages you visit, what you click on, when you perform those actions, what language preference you have, and so on.

  * **Device and browser data**

We collect information from the devices you use to access our services. Device data mainly means your IP address, operating system version, device type, system and performance information, and browser type.

  * **Information from page tags**

PurelyHR and our third-party partners, such as our advertising and analytics partners, use cookies and other tracking technologies (e.g., web beacons, device identifiers and pixels) to provide functionality and to recognize you across different services and devices. We provide more information on cookies below and in our Cookies Policy.

  * **Data logs**

Like most websites today, our web servers keep log files that record data each time a device accesses those servers. The log files contain data about the nature of each access, including originating IP addresses, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system versions, device type and timestamps.

  * **Referral information**

If you arrive at a PurelyHR website from an external source (such as a link on another website or in an email), we record information about the source that referred you to us.

#### If you are a Creator we will also collect:

  * **Registration information**

When you register for a PurelyHR account, we collect a company name, your first and last name, a username, a password and an email address.

  * **Billing information**

If you make a payment to PurelyHR, we require you to provide your billing details, a name, address, email address and financial information corresponding to your selected method of payment (e.g. a credit card number and expiration date).

  * **Account settings**

You can set various preferences in your User Preferences page. For example, your default date format, time zone and communication preferences (e.g. opting in or out of receiving marketing communications from PurelyHR).

#### If you are a User:

  * Creators, who are your data controllers, and probably your employer, have access to provide personal information in their PurelyHR account, on your behalf. PurelyHR does not control which information is provided in the account. Please refer to your employer’s privacy policy, which applies to the collection, use, processing and retention of your personal information.

## 3\. How We Use The Information We Collect

**We process personal data about you where:**

  * **You have consented or;**
  * **PurelyHR has legitimate interests in:**
    * **Improving service experience; and**
    * **Developing new products and service features.**

In each of the instances where we describe how we use your data in this privacy policy, we have identified which of these grounds for processing we are relying upon.

When you have consented we collect and use the following information about you:

  * **Contact Information**

We use contact information to respond to your inquiries, send you information as part of the services, and send you marketing information (as long as you have agreed to this at the point of providing your information and for as long as you do not opt-out).

    * **Example:** We provide your email address to a member of our sales team or customer success team who will contact you if you submitted an inquiry through one of the online forms on our site. 
  * **Cookies - page tags and web beacons**

We collect information from page tags and web beacons to allow us to determine the success of our advertising campaigns. For more information please read our Cookies Policy.

    * **Example:** To personalize marketing campaigns run through third party advertisers and help PurelyHR measure online advertising success and to deliver ads for our services based on user preferences. See our cookies section. If you do not want PurelyHR to use this information to serve you targeted ads about our services, you may indicate your preferences at <https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/> or, if you are located in the European Union, at <https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>. You may continue to receive ads over the internet that are not based on information you provided to PurelyHR.
  * **How you use our services**

We use information about how you have interacted with our website to improve our services for you and all users.

    * **Example:** We collect information about the web pages you have visited and your activity on our website. We collect this information so that we can track the most visited and most useful parts of our website to identify what are our most popular services. 

**We process your personal information in the following categories of data for legitimate interests pursued by us, which are described in detail in this privacy policy. We have undertaken to ensure that we place clear limitations on each of these uses so that your privacy is respected and only the information necessary to achieve these legitimate aims is used. Our primary goal is to improve our services, while also ensuring that personal information of all users is respected and protected.**

  * **Device data**  
We use device data both to troubleshoot problems with our service and to make improvements to it. 
    * **Example:** We collect device and browser information from you to troubleshoot website functionality issues and to fix bugs.
  * **Log data** We use log data for many different business purposes to include: 
    * To monitor abuse and troubleshoot.
    * To fix bugs and troubleshoot product functionality. 
      * **Example:** Your browser type to determine how we can present our website best within that browser environment.
  * **Referral information**  
We use referral information to track the success of our integrations and referral processes. 
    * **Example:** If you clicked on an advertisement for PurelyHR, presented by one of our partners on the web, which brought you to our website, we will record this information to help us track the success of advertising campaigns. 
  * **To manage our services** we will also internally use your information and data, for the following limited purposes: 
    * To enforce our agreements where applicable.
    * To prevent potentially illegal activities.
    * To screen for and prevent undesirable or abusive activity. For example, we have automated systems that screen content for phishing activities, spam, and fraud.
  * **Legal uses**

To respond to legal requests or prevent fraud, we may need to disclose any information or data we hold about you. If we receive a legal request, we may need to inspect the data we hold to determine how to respond.

**We process personal data about you either with your consent or in order to:**

  * **Fulfill our contractual responsibility to deliver the services to you;**
  * **To pursue PurelyHR’s legitimate interests in:**
    * **Improving service experience; and**
    * **Developing new products and service features.**

In each of the instances where we describe how we use your data in this privacy policy, we have identified which of these grounds for processing we are relying upon.

You have consented to us using certain types of cookies on our websites. In particular we use:

  * **Cookies - page tags and web beacons**  
We collect information from page tags and web beacons to allow us to determine the success of our advertising campaigns. For more information please read our Cookies Policy. 

**We process your personal information in the following categories of data for legitimate interests pursued by us, which are described in detail in this privacy policy. We have undertaken to ensure that we place clear limitations on each of these uses so that your privacy is respected and only the information necessary to achieve these legitimate aims is used. Our primary goal is to improve our services, while also ensuring that personal information of all users is respected and protected.**

  * **Contact Information**

We use contact information to respond to your inquiries, send you information as part of the services, and send you marketing information (for as long as you do not opt-out). We use your email address to send you marketing (newsletters), unless you indicate a preference to opt-out and for general updates on your account. You can opt out of marketing communications at any time by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in them, or changing the relevant setting on your My Preferences page.

  * **How you use our services**

We use information about how you have interacted with our website to improve our services for you and all users.

  * **Device data**

We use device data both to troubleshoot problems with our service and to make improvements to it. We collect this to help us improve your service experience through a specific browser by optimizing how the website looks in a particular browser, and to ensure the service operates optimally and as it should on different devices and browsers.

  * **Log data**

We use log data for many different business purposes to include:

    * To monitor abuse and troubleshoot.
    * To fix bugs and troubleshoot product functionality.

Your IP address is used to determine where an unknown/unauthorized access may have occurred in your account (abuse monitoring).

  * **Referral information**

We use referral information to track the success of our integrations and referral processes.

  * **Third parties and integrations**

We will collect and use information from third parties and integration partners to:

    * Ensure you can sign-up to our service from a third party integration like Facebook/LinkedIn/Microsoft/Google/SSO; 
    * To personalize our services for you; and
    * Ensure you can use our service in conjunction with other services.
  * **To manage our services** we will also internally use your information and data, for the following limited purposes: 
    * To enforce our agreements where applicable.
    * To prevent potentially illegal activities.
    * To screen for and prevent undesirable or abusive activity. For example, we have automated systems that screen content for phishing activities, spam, and fraud.
  * **Legal uses**

To respond to legal requests or prevent fraud, we may need to disclose any information or data we hold about you. If we receive a legal request, we may need to inspect the data we hold to determine how to respond.

**We collect and use the following data on the basis that we have to use this information in order to fulfill our contract with you:**

  * **Account Information**

We need to use your account data to run your account, provide you with services, bill you for our services, provide you with customer support, and contact you about your service or account. We occasionally send you communications of a transactional nature (e.g. service-related announcements, billing-related matters, changes to our services or policies, a welcome email when you first register). You cannot opt out of these communications since they are required to provide our services to you.

**We process personal data about you either with your consent or in order to:**

  * **Fulfill our contractual responsibility to deliver the services to you;**
  * **To pursue PurelyHR’s legitimate interests of:**
    * **Improving service experience; and**
    * **Developing new products and service features.**

In each of the instances where we describe how we use your data in this privacy policy, we have identified which of these grounds for processing we are relying upon.

You have consented to us using certain types of cookies on our websites. In particular we use:

  * **Cookies - page tags and web beacons** We collect information from page tags and web beacons to allow us to determine the success of our advertising campaigns. For more information please read our Cookies Policy. 

**We process your personal information in the following categories of data for legitimate interests pursued by us, which are described in detail in this privacy policy. We have undertaken to ensure that we place clear limitations on each of these uses so that your privacy is respected and only the information necessary to achieve these legitimate aims is used. Our primary goal is to improve our services, while also ensuring that personal information of all users is respected and protected.**

  * **Contact Information**  
We use contact information to respond to your inquiries, send you information and communication as part of the services. **Example:** We will send you an email when one of your time-off requests is approved. 
  * **How you use our services**  
We use information about how you have interacted with our website to improve our services for you and all users. 
  * **Device data**  
We use device data both to troubleshoot problems with our service and to make improvements to it. We collect this to help us improve your service experience through a specific browser by optimizing how the website looks in a particular browser, and to ensure the service operates optimally and as it should on different devices and browsers. 
  * **Log data**  
We use log data for many different business purposes to include: 
    * To monitor abuse and troubleshoot.
    * To fix bugs and troubleshoot product functionality.
  * **Third parties and integrations**  
We will collect and use information from third parties and integration partners to: 
    * Ensure you can sign-up to our service from a third party integration like Facebook/LinkedIn/Microsoft/Google/SSO;
    * To personalize our services for you; and
    * Ensure you can use our service in conjunction with other services.
  * **To manage our services** we will also internally use your information and data, for the following limited purposes: To enforce our agreements where applicable. 
    * To prevent potentially illegal activities.
    * To screen for and prevent undesirable or abusive activity. For example, we have automated systems that screen content for phishing activities, spam, and fraud.
  * **Legal uses**  
To respond to legal requests or prevent fraud, we may need to disclose any information or data we hold about you. If we receive a legal request, we may need to inspect the data we hold to determine how to respond. 

We do not share your information or data with third parties outside PurelyHR except in the following limited circumstances:

  * To help us provide certain aspects of our services we use trusted key partners – in particular, we engage third parties to: 
    * Manage our sales and customer support services to you.
    * Deliver and help us track our marketing and advertising content.
    * Help us track website conversion success metrics.
    * Provide hosting, maintenance, backup, storage and virtual infrastructure.

We enter into confidentiality and data processing terms with partners to ensure they comply with high levels of confidentiality and best practice in privacy and security standards and we regularly review these standards and practices.

  * We also have to share information or data in order to: 
    * Comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, including to meet national security requirements.
    * Enforce our agreements, policies and terms of service.
    * Protect the security or integrity of our products and services.
    * Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of our users, the public or to PurelyHR and/or as required or permitted by law.

## 5\. Cookies

We and our partners use cookies and similar technologies on our websites. For more information see our Cookies Policy.

We use certain cookies, as described in our Cookies Policy and here in our Privacy Policy, that you agree to when you use our website and, in the case of some cookies, for legitimate interests of delivering and optimizing our services (where the cookie delivers essential functionality). Cookies are small bits of data we store on the device you use to access our services so we can recognize repeat users. Each cookie expires after a certain period of time, depending on what we use it for. We use cookies and similar technologies for several reasons:

  * **To make our site easier to use**

Creators and Users, if you use the “Remember me” feature when you sign into your account, we store your username and companyID in a cookie to make it quicker for you to sign in whenever you return to PurelyHR.

  * **For security reasons**

We use cookies to authenticate your identity and confirm whether you are currently logged into PurelyHR or determine if an incident impacts you.

  * **To advertise to you**

We, or our service providers and other third parties we work with, place cookies when you visit our website and other websites or when you open emails that we send you, in order to provide you with more tailored marketing content (about our services or other services), and to evaluate whether this content is useful or effective. If you don’t want to receive ads that are tailored to you based on your online activity, you may "opt out" of many of the companies that are involved in such tailoring by going to [https://www.aboutads.info](https://www.aboutads.info/), <https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/> or, if you’re located in the European Union, at [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Opting out in this way does not mean you will not receive any ads; it just means that you will not receive ads from such companies that have been tailored to you based on your activities and inferred preferences.

  * **Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a website monitoring tool that allows users to see volumes of website visitors, their source, and to analyse how the content of their website is viewed and navigated. Visitors to our websites may opt out of certain types of Google Analytics tracking. If you do not wish to participate in Google Analytics, you may also download the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on : <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

## 6\. Security

You can find everything related to how we tackle security by following the link.

## 7\. Data Retention

If you are a Creator and hold an account with PurelyHR, we do not delete the data in your account – you are responsible for and control the time periods for which you retain this data. There are controls in your account where you can delete data at a User level.

If you are a Creator, we also retain some of your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, to enforce our agreements, to support business operations and to continue to develop and improve our Services. Where we retain information for Service improvement and development, we take steps to eliminate information that directly identifies you, and we only use the information to uncover collective insights about the use of our Services, not to specifically analyze personal characteristics about you.

If you are a User (employee), you will need to ask the Creator (your data controller) how long your data will be stored in our services.

## 8\. Safety of Minors

Our services are not intended for and may not be used by minors. “Minors” are individuals under the age of 13 (or under a higher age if permitted by the laws of their residence). PurelyHR does not knowingly collect personal data from Minors or allow them to register. If it comes to our attention that we have collected personal data from a Minor, we may delete this information without notice. If you have reason to believe that this has occurred, please contact customer support.

## 9\. Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will notify account holders of significant changes in the way we treat any personal information, by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your PurelyHR account. We may also place a prominent notice on our website. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## 10\. Who Is My Data Controller?

As mentioned above – all personal information at the User level is controlled by the Creator.

## 11\. Your Rights

Some of you (in particular, European Users) have certain legal rights to obtain information about whether we hold personal information about them, to access personal information we hold about them, and to obtain its correction, update, amendment or deletion in appropriate circumstances. If you seek to express any of the following rights, you should direct your request to your employer, who is a customer of ours. Your employer is able to delete and update personal information and data without our involvement.

Rights which you are entitled to are:

  * Data access rights
  * Right to restrict processing
  * Right of Rectification
  * Right to Erasure (Right to be Forgotten)
  * Right to object to processing
  * Right to withdraw consent; and
  * Data portability rights

### 11.1 Creators

If you hold an account with PurelyHR, you are entitled to a copy of all data which we hold in relation to you. You are also entitled to request that we restrict how we use your data or object to some aspect of our treatment of your data. You can access a lot of your data in your own account when you log in. However, if you want to obtain a full copy of all your data or to request a restriction / limitation in how we use your data, please [contact our customer support team](mailto:support@purelyhr.com).

### 11.2 Users

If you are an employee of an account that was created by a Creator, you are entitled to a copy of all personal data which we hold in relation to you. You can access and download all of your personal data in your own account when you log in.

### 11.3 Visitors

If you have visited our website and you want to exercise any of the above rights please [contact our customer support team](mailto:support@purelyhr.com). Alternatively if your request is for the right to be forgotten as it relates only to our use of cookies you can achieve this by clearing the cookies in your browser settings.

## 12\. Exercising Your Rights

Our contact information for privacy inquiries

Ironflow Technologies Inc.  
312 Champlain St.  
Dieppe, NB, E1A 1P3  
Canada
